Is anyone going to riot?
Is anyone going to try to shoot them in the face?
Are they going to try to attack them in the street?
They would say this is great.
This is amazing.
Thank you for the resources.
There might be concern among the community,
especially if American citizens are being —
especially if American citizens are caught up in that,
which some reportedly were.
Yeah, we netted over 30 foreign terrorists
who are members of trained Iraqis who, by the way,
they torture women and children.
Those American citizens are now safe from trained Iraqis.
You know, there was a case recently in Washington State
where trained Iraqis took a power drill.
But isn't that enough reason for some people to demonstrate
and say that they disagree with that policy?
They took a power drill.
Isn't it enough for some people —